hosco.com 2014-10-29

# Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy discloses how we treat the information we collect when you use the HOSCO Site and how you can manage it. 

_Last update 16.06.2011_

### 1- Information collected

We collect personal information on a strictly voluntary basis:

a. When you register an account on the Platform: including but not limited to, your name, your school or company, your city and country, your email and a password.  
b. When you complete or edit your profile with further information about yourself or your organization. This information may also include attachments you upload to your profile, such as your resume, diploma, cover letters or endorsement letters for candidates, and, for companies and hotel schools, items such as news, articles, videos and pictures. Providing further information about yourself beyond what is expressly required is on a voluntary basis. Keep in mind that if you decide not to share certain information, you may not take full benefit of the Platform possibilities.  
c. When you use certain Platform applications, interact with third party applications, click on ads, respond to questionnaires, participate in contests, or register for promotions. 

Credit card information you may provide when you make online orders on the Site is processed though a third-party credit card service company which uses encryption to protect your credit card information. HOSCO does not store any such information. 

We may also collect non-personal information on a strictly voluntary basis. We may use such non-personal information to improve the Site, customize your experience on the Platform and share this information with third parties, but only in aggregate with non-identifiable information provided. 

### 2- Uses of information collected

Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, HOSCO does not sell, rent, share or otherwise provide your personal information with any third parties for marketing purposes without your consent. 

We use the information you provide to:

a. Give you access to the functions, applications and services of the Platform.  
b. Enable you to communicate with other Users and HOSCO.  
c. Communicate with you.

Customize the service provided to you and other Users.   
Manage items such as questionnaires, contests and promotions.   
Provide Users and third parties with relevant anonymous statistics on the Platform and its Users.   
Fulfill legal and any other necessary requirements.   
HOSCO may work with third-party companies and provide them with your personal information to perform functions and services on its behalf, for example, to process credit card payments and to provide customer service and marketing assistance. These third-party companies are bound to maintain the strictest confidentiality of your information.   
Third-party websites may have links posted on HOSCO, but they are not subject to this Privacy Policy and therefore you should review their own privacy policy in order to determine how they treat User information.   
You have the right at any time to withdraw your consent to HOSCO to collect and process your information by changing your Account Settings or by closing your account. However, you acknowledge that such withdrawal will not be retroactive and Users who have had access to your information may have retained a copy of your profile or other content in their own files. HOSCO cannot be held responsible for the retention or future use of such information by third parties. 

### 3- Your control of the information collected

You may edit the personal information submitted at any time in your profile. 

You may control at any time what type of information is visible and accessible to other Users through your Account Settings and you agree and acknowledge that certain basic information about you and each User of the Site will be included, visible and accessible to any Users in the respective public profiles on the Site. 

You may control at any time what kind of communication and notification is sent to you through your Account Settings. 

HOSCO has defined default visibility and notification settings and Users are encouraged to adjust and review them in accordance with their preferences upon registration as well as on a regular basis when using the Site. 

You can close your account by simply clicking on “Deactivate Account” in your Account Settings. Your personal information will then be removed from the visible section of the Site and HOSCO may delete all of your account. Certain information and content generated or submitted by you may be kept for legal or business purposes or simply to ensure the continued service, functions and applications of the Site for other Users. HOSCO disclaims any liability in relation to the deletion or retention of information. 

### 4- Opt-Out

Following your registration and during your use of the Site, you may receive emails from HOSCO on services updates, industry trends, and any other items that you did not expressly request. An email address will be provided to you with such communications to request no future notices of this kind from HOSCO. 

### 5- Cookies

HOSCO may make use of cookies to track site usage and trends and generally to improve the quality of the Site. You can remove or block cookies in your browser settings. 

### 6- IP addresses

When Users use the Site, we collect standard information such as their IP addresses and use such data in an anonymous and collective manner to analyse trends and more generally to improve the quality of the Site. 

### 7- Children and Minors

Children are strictly not eligible to use the Site and we request that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. 

### 8- Business Transitions

In the event that HOSCO goes through a merger or acquisition (all or a portion) by another company, User information will be part of the assets transferred and the newly formed/buying company will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information provided. 

### 9- Security

Access to your HOSCO account and information is protected by a username and password. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of this login information and for controlling access to your account. 

The personal information you provide is stored on restricted servers. However, the Internet is not a fully secure environment and there is no guarantee that information may not be viewed, disclosed, altered, destroyed or used for any improper purposes by breach of our safeguards. 

### 10- Changes to this Privacy Policy

HOSCO reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without advance notice, and the modified versions of this policy will be posted on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the publication of the revised policy on the Site shall constitute your consent to the changes. 

### 11- How to contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Site in general, please contact us online at info@hosco.com or mail us at: 

_Hospitality Connection  
Rue du Village-Suisse 10   
1205 Geneva   
Switzerland_
